ACTWU Publications 5619 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 11, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Times, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    By Chicago and Central States Joint Board, ACTWU. v.17:no.2 (1995/1995: Winter). Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Partners In Prevention: Health and Safety Action Manual for Local Unions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By Department of Occupational Safety and Health, ACTWU. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Stitching Post, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By ACTWU Local 2573. v.3:no.3 (1995). Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Reflections, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By Rochester Regional Joint Board, ACTWU. v.12:no.53 (1994:Winter). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Reflections, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By Rochester Regional Joint Board, ACTWU. v.12:no.54 (1995:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Reflections, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By Rochester Regional Joint Board, ACTWU. v.13:no.57 (1995:Winter). Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: What They Wore: Highlights of Fashion History, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU); Leon Stein. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Bargaining On Women's Issues and Family Concerns: Clauses From ACTWU Contracts, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
    By Research Department, ACTWU. Second Edition, November, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Domestic Violence: A Guide for Union Action, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
    By New York City Labor Union; Coalition Against Domestic Violence; Cornell University; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Your Money's Worth, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
    By Sidney Margolius. Consumer Tips To Economy. Item is in English.